To live is to die.
The Grandmother is a animation, horror film directed by David Lynch.
To escape neglect and abuse from his parents, a young boy plants
some strange seeds and they grow into a grandmother.
Grandmother, played by Dorothy McGinnis.
Mother, played by Virginia Maitland.
Father, played by Robert Chadwick.
Boy, played by Richard White.
The Short Films of David Lynch (2002) is a DVD collection of the early student
and commissioned film work of American filmmaker David Lynch.
As such, the collection does not include Lynch's later short
works, which are listed in the filmography.
The DVD contains introductions by Lynch to each film.
The film explores themes of surreal, surrealism, black and white.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.